(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2 Extra Episode=
(Back to Auckland from Queenstown)
When we were in Auckland earlier,
the Blue Tears trip was canceled
due to the weather.
They say the weather today
gives us a chance to see them.
Anyone who wants to try their luck
can go and experience it.
The moon is flat today.
Like it got slapped
on the back of the head.
A moon with a flat back of the head.
(Keith, Guide)
- Hello.
So welcome to Long Bay
on this coast base of Auckland.
My name is Keith.
- Keith.
So we will equip you with
a personal flotation device.
This is in case you fall into the water.
Okay.
Let's hope we don't have to use them.
So in the water,
(Blue Tears: bioluminescence from plankton)
you will see some plankton,
(The most common type is a plankton
called Noctiluca scintillans)
(Disturbed by waves, fish, and boats)
which shine as you move your hands through the water,
(they emit a blue glow)
and it reminds me
of electricity on the water.
And we call that
"Plankton Galaxy".
It reminds us of a galaxy in space.
Looking forward to it.
So magical.
Yes, let's take more photos
and send them to the group.
So they can see them.
Make them jealous.
Yeah, okay.
Thank you.
Let's take a selfie first.
Come on.
One on each side.
Let's go.
(Filmed under safety precautions)
Is it cold?
Not very cold. It's fine.
Good.
Okay.
Good job.
Turn around.
Okay.
Alright.
That's fine?
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
It feels very easy to paddle.
(Liu Yuning, Guo Jingfei, Wang Yuwen)
Hi.
You follow us.
Okay.
Follow me.
Alright, are we ready to go?
Yes.
Ready to go.
Go, go, go.
Don't you think
being out on the sea at night
is a magical experience?
This is my first time.
My first time too.
The sea at night is actually terrifying.
Yeah.
If you were alone,
you'd always feel like
something might surface.
A monster would come up
and just eat you.
We're gonna number us first.
We're gonna get numbers.
I'll be one.
You can be two.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Okay.
The banana is three.
Banana.
Let's go.
Let's go chase the Blue Tears.
Look, the stars are all lit up now.
So beautiful.
The Milky Way.
And we can see
the Southern Cross tonight.
The New Zealand flag
has the Southern Cross on it.
Okay.
One, two, three, four.
Yeah, one, two, three, four.
And the two pointers.
Up to the left.
That's the constellation of Orion.
(Orion's Belt)
Orion.
Where are you going?
Slow down.
Is your little boat of friendship
still stable?
It feels like it's
about to capsize.
About to capsize?
That helps to trigger the bio.
Is there any?
Not yet.
Why are you exclaiming?
I thought you saw it.
He meant,
generally, when you paddle like this,
you can see it.
But it's not happening yet.
We can go a bit further in.
- Go a bit further in.
- Now it's the "exception".
The "generally" didn't happen.
Is it just my imagination?
I think it glows
when the water's stirred.
Or is it just the moonlight?
It's the moonlight.
The people rowing
under the moonlight.
It's quite romantic.
Yes.
I think I see it.
It's like tiny diamonds, sparkling.
The big blue.
Do you see it?
It's like the Milky Way.
Look.
I see it.
Like lightning.
Like lightning, yes.
There's more here.
There's more. Look.
Yeah.
Come on.
Look at this side.
See?
Fantastic.
Come over here. It's so obvious.
Beautiful, right?
Beautiful. Right.
So beautiful.
Bro, look at this water.
Beautiful.
Can you see it?
I see it.
It's so obvious.
There's a lot here. Come quickly.
There's already some under your boat.
There's a lot under their boat.
Yeah.
There's been a blue glow
under their boat.
This is amazing.
This one, right?
Not bad at all.
So beautiful.
More on this side.
Look at my hand.
See?
How is it?
This is beautiful.
Number two.
Here.
Did you film it?
I'll film it.
Why is it gone again?
It was just there.
Are they like little sprites?
They ran away.
Yes, they drift around.
On the left. Our left.
It's here now.
It's all over here.
There's a lot here.
More on this side.
A sky full of stars.
Hands full of Blue Tears.
It's very rare.
You really have to see this in person.
Yes.
We had to paddle quite a long way
to get to the good bio.
Bioluminescents. But it was worth it.
This is very worth it.
Perfect.
Yeah.
It was actually quite worth it, I think.
At least I feel very happy.
We've never rowed a boat
to watch stars at night.
Right. I think this is very meaningful.
Yes.
The only weird thing is us two.
Alright, it's all about brotherhood.
Of course.
The little boat of friendship
won't capsize.
We're literally in the same boat.
(May this stunning blue become
gentle starlight in future dreams)
(Streets of Paris)
Where is Song Qian?
(You made me wait so long)
Why isn't she here yet?
The weather is quite cold.
The longer I wait,
the less romantic it gets.
What's going on?
(Your romantic partner has arrived)
It's you?
Today, you're my romantic partner.
Can you imagine...
Can you imagine this?
Don't lie to me.
Where is Song Qian?
The one you were
(My feelings were misplaced after all)
waiting for was Song Qian?
What's going on here?
Is this a mistake?
No.
(Very certain)
This is our...
This is our token.
Really?
Yes. Are you dissatisfied
or what?
I'm not dissatisfied.
If you are, I'd text Song Qian.
I'd call her over.
Do we really need
to be together every day?
I don't know.
(It must be a special fate)
Anyway, it's probably fate.
We're together for both dramas
and variety shows.
That's true.
I don't know.
But is it true?
Of course.
But our roses are not
the same size.
Do they match?
Yes.
They tried
to get two similar ones.
It's okay.
Is it okay?
Is it really us two?
Today, it's us two.
Great, Yuning.
Don't...
I can't tell.
I can't tell that you think it's great.
Is my EQ high?
It's okay.
Your reaction
is very fast.
My reaction is very fast?
Here.
Honglei, you read it.
Give me the flower.
Mission card.
Through the crowded streets of Paris,
fate brought you together.
It is quite fateful.
Fateful.
Making you each other's
romantic partners.
Next, please cooperate to complete
the tribute mission
for a romantic French film
and create a romantic atmosphere
unique to you.
We are definitely a comedy.
Okay.
What is the movie called?
Léon: The Professional.
Léon: The Professional?
Then who plays the killer?
Either is fine.
You play the killer.
Then who do you play?
Do you play the main villain?
No, the little girl.
She is...
It's actually just a walking scene.
But you are so tall.
How can you play this little girl?
I'll walk behind.
I'll walk crouching.
You'll walk crouching?
Honglei, you misunderstood.
You are Mathilda.
You memorized the wrong lines.
(Trying to convince himself)
But in terms of height,
I think this is appropriate.
Yes. Right.
Alright then.
Let's use our Northeast dialect then.
Yep.
Don't do this kind of stupid thing.
- Did you hear me?
- Yep.
If it were me,
I wouldn't do it that way.
Wouldn't do it that way.
That's not professional.
This profession has its rules.
Yep.
And don't always say "yep".
Why all the "yeps"?
Yep.
Good.
Let's go.
(Setting off to film)
I'll take the case.
You hold the plant.
You...
(Strong wind incoming)
It's windy today.
See? Even the heavens don't agree.
The wind has picked up.
I'm playing Mathilda.
What about the hairstyle?
I need that...
What's that hairstyle?
Bob cut.
I don't have a bob cut.
No wig, right?
I only have the Honglei cut.
(No wig, but there is a necklace)
This...
This is that kind of...
This is the necklace Mathilda wears?
A classic necklace.
You can wear it as a bow tie.
Why do I feel like
Yuning is going to choke me?
So romantic.
I can't take it.
I feel like we're here to film a drama.
Exactly, like we are back on set.
Yeah.
Together every day.
(Rehearsing)
Don't be silly all day long.
Or else I'll give you a punch.
Did you hear me?
Yep.
If I were you,
I wouldn't be so unprofessional.
These are the rules of the game.
Yep.
Can you stop saying "yep"?
Okay.
Let's go.
Just like that.
Your lines are good.
Pretty good.
(Satisfied)
(After the short film shoot)
Two idiots, right?
And you were wiggling.
(Reviewing the footage)
It's pretty good.
Okay.
Pleasure working with you.
Second collaboration.
- It's already the second drama.
- The second drama is finished. Alright.
Second collaboration complete.
Okay.
Is this the place for me?
Fei,
this is the scene where you
and your partner meet.
I was scared.
I thought this was my partner.
(Plush teddy bear)
It is looking at me very affectionately.
How nice.
This old building.
Let me think.
I think logically
it should be Song Qian.
(Another one hoping for Qian)
I'm the one she knows best here.
Judging by the food,
it doesn't feel like a girl.
This...
This is so fierce.
Judging by the food,
it feels like only Liu Tianzuo
would come over.
Are all these the small French coffees?
But it's not bad.
It tastes very good.
Why are there three cups of coffee here?
(The mysterious third cup of coffee)
That cup
isn't ours, right?
Anyway, we are all acquaintances.
I don't think I need to be so polite.
I can eat my dessert first.
The ice cream is about to melt.
This isn't being impolite, guys.
It's my respect for the chef.
I think this dessert
is very similar to me.
(Savoring it carefully)
It's so delicious.
This might have been chosen
by Sun Honglei.
He would do this.
He wouldn't pick a hoe.
(Wishing sincerely)
But I hope it's a girl,
to be honest.
Right.
Why isn't
(Waiting anxiously)
my partner here yet?
(At this moment, your partner)
Oh, no, my eyesight is bad.
(Can't seem to find you)
Oh, no.
(The long road to finding the partner)
This is so mysterious.
Cover my face.
(Found him?)
Walk forward.
(Your Naiwen is coming)
Is he here?
Tell him not to make any sound.
The person I originally imagined
has white hair.
(Matches the imagination)
He has a calm and steady personality
and a reserved temperament.
Because opposite me is a piece of glass,
but it's also a mirror at the same time.
It has a reflection.
(Close-up appearance description)
Let's make contact.
When you found out it was me,
were you regretful too?
- Don't force yourself to laugh.
- You know what?
I really don't regret it.
You want to be with me?
Yes.
Being with you,
I believe I am the most relaxed.
Yes, we even held hands.
(Must have a sense of ceremony)
Shouldn't we make contact?
(Satisfying you)
Bonjour.
Do we still need to make contact?
How about this?
A romantic place
needs a romantic
meeting ceremony.
French style.
Come on.
Bonjour.
(The bears also need a French greeting)
What you said was "oh, yo".
Come on.
Both sides.
Yes, both sides.
Right.
Well,
how did you guess it was me?
There's a reflection here.
Really?
You know what?
If they hadn't reminded me,
I would have walked past.
Because my eyesight is bad.
- I didn't know who it was.
- And you were blocking with the bear.
(Buffs stacked)
And I didn't know where I was going.
They only told me it was nearby.
I even walked around
that park over there.
Then your task
was more tiring than mine.
Then I saw a girl.
Her height was a bit like Yuwen.
But she was walking a dog.
But I thought
maybe it was her disguise.
Her disguise.
But to be honest,
I really couldn't see clearly.
When I got closer and looked,
it was indeed a foreigner.
Taste yours.
Okay.
What is this called again?
This?
This is called an egg tart.
No.
What kind of egg tart was it?
It's called Naiwen egg tart.
We should
thank this era
for the good life we live.
We even get to eat caramel macchiato.
In our impression,
(Memories of the era)
the only desserts were sugar flatbreads.
Donkey rolls.
In Tianjin, it's sugar fried dough.
Similar to donkey rolls.
Tianjin also has something
called sugar triangles.
- Steamed buns with brown sugar inside?
- Yes.
Yes, but it's triangles.
Beijing is the same.
Is this our mission today?
No problem.
(Easy win)
For us,
professional actors, it's no problem.
I even made a bet in the car.
What bet?
I said I guessed it was Wang Yuwen.
I said if I won,
I would decide the next episode's guest.
Now, I...
Look.
Do I have any...
Do I have any changes?
(Expecting)
Don't compare me with this photo.
Compare me with my last recording.
Say it out loud.
Say it to the audience.
Don't be so stingy.
(I'll say)
He has lost weight.
His face is tighter too.
Am I getting closer?
And then...
Forget it.
It's okay.
This is my earliest photo.
When you were young...
Do you hate your past self so much?
It's not hate.
Mine simply can't compare to yours.
Come on.
(Starting rehearsal)
Has it started?
Wait.
How about this?
We two...
I'll order food first.
We should first...
We should meet first.
After we meet, you leave,
and I'll piece it together here.
Otherwise,
after I finish piecing it together,
how can I turn around
and know it's you?
I think this is more reasonable.
Great.
Let's go.
I've been waiting for ten minutes.
Right?
Ten minutes.
This baguette is like
a stick of incense.
The later she comes,
(Hoping to see my partner
before finishing it)
the less baguette there'll be left.
It's really delicious.
(Qian is here)
Let me search for my partner.
Is he by the Seine River?
It's either Fei or Xingxu.
It's
a man.
Very tall.
Is it Yuning?
Or Lin Yi?
His walking style
is a bit like Chen Xingxu.
His hairstyle is also
a bit like Chen Xingxu.
It's really you.
Mr. Chen.
We are quite well-matched today.
I've already eaten it.
Did you hollow it out?
Hello, I'm the rabbit.
Just now...
I just told them.
I said...
I said it took you so long to find me.
I've been waiting here
for about ten minutes.
Is our show fun?
So sudden.
It's just started,
and then you ask me, "Well?
Is our show fun?"
Well, your subtext is actually saying,
"Well?
Are you satisfied with your partner?"
Yes, that's what I mean.
(Rehearsing lines)
Look over here, Notre-Dame de Paris.
Do you believe Notre-Dame de Paris
will disappear one day?
There was once another church here.
Right here.
Actually, being a tourist isn't bad.
I'll say all the lines in the middle?
Yes.
Let me take a look.
Let me look at my lines.
There are lines here.
It feels like these two people...
Are they having a conversation?
I'll say,
"Look over here, Notre-Dame de Paris."
Wow.
Do these two people have to say "wow"?
Hurry, say "wow".
Wow.
Look over here,
Notre-Dame de Paris.
Wow.
How do we dance?
Do you know?
How to dance?
Let's see.
(Learning the dance)
There's music.
Get in on the beat?
Look.
Say hello.
Forward.
Backward.
Then spin around.
Did you see the exchange?
The exchange.
Then forward again.
Then backward.
The exchange.
Spin around.
Then...
Then separate our gazes.
Then like this. Like this.
Then like this.
Like this.
- Then you spin around again alone.
- Then spin around again.
Then we run forward.
We hold hands
and run towards the camera.
It has this...
(Not missing any detail)
Then we run towards the camera.
Right.
(Dance crash course completed)
Almost there.
Okay.
So where are we going?
To the sign over there.
To the sign that says six.
Okay.
Where is it?
I really didn't expect
that one day
I'd be traveling in Paris with you.
Really.
Really, this is too...
- This is too amazing.
- Right.
So we have to live a little longer.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about me.
They have a platform there.
It's like this.
And there's a bit of blocking and stuff.
Yes.
Then we can use this pole
as that thing.
Sure.
Yes, I'll lean on it.
We can point like this.
- Right?
- Yes.
Okay.
I feel like we are the least efficient
among all the groups, right?
We're the noisiest.
Hurry up. Come on.
The ugliest?
The noisiest.
That's you.
Come on.
Let's try it.
We can try it.
We need to do a camera rehearsal.
Yes, let's do a rehearsal.
(Rehearsing in a noisy way)
Wow, look over there.
There's Notre-Dame de Paris over there.
Do you believe Notre-Dame de Paris
will disappear one day?
(Sense of belief)
Actually, there was another church
before.
Right here.
There's one more line.
You forgot?
I didn't.
I was just blocking.
Okay.
I've almost forgotten.
What were the lines?
I...
See? You forgot the lines.
Look, I've already
forgotten how beautiful Paris is.
(Rehearsing Before Sunset)
I've almost forgotten
how beautiful Paris is.
Yes.
(Instantly turns into an action movie)
Is this a suspense drama?
(Romantic drama suddenly turned
into a suspense thriller)
Then you come up from the river
and seek revenge.
You'll say...
Actually, being a tourist like this
is pretty nice.
Actually, being a tourist like this...
(Made himself laugh)
(Wen arrives at the meeting point)
A beautiful bookstore.
Where's my romantic partner?
(Perfect match)
They go so well with my outfit today.
When I see him later,
I'll say,
"Bonjour."
I'll give this to him.
For my romantic partner.
He's flying a small plane.
I wish for him to fly freely
and be free and happy.
And there's a little fox on his head.
I hope he has
his
pets, family, or friends
to accompany him.
How do I look?
Do I need to tidy up?
Tidy up my outfit?
(Ready and set)
He's here?
Where?
Right at this moment.
Are you my romantic partner?
I'm not.
Why are you wearing red?
- Why are you wearing red?
- Such a coincidence?
Hello.
Right, I forgot my introduction.
Bonjour.
This is for you.
What's this?
This is the Little Prince.
A Little Prince also in red?
Yes.
A small plane.
This is
the role of the pilot
- you played.
- He Xi?
He Xi.
This is Gaba.
(So thoughtful)
I made it up on the spot.
Where did you get it?
Didn't you buy it here?
I bought it here.
But I didn't bring anything.
Don't give it to me.
Look, it's such a coincidence today.
Why are we both wearing red?
Who else?
Just us.
We really didn't discuss it.
(No communication, pure coincidence)
I didn't even know when he arrived.
This is
destiny.
Okay.
Mission card.
This is too easy.
Do we still need to build chemistry?
Do we still need
to build the atmosphere?
We need the atmosphere.
- Do we need it?
- We need the atmosphere.
Isn't it all just atmosphere with us
just standing here?
All atmosphere, no substance.
No substance?
We have all chemistry, no atmosphere.
Right.
Okay, let's go then.
(Rehearsing)
- Okay.
We just dance.
Have you seen this movie?
I have.
What is he doing over there?
The two of them are dancing.
Okay.
Nail it.
Just let all the romantic male leads
you've played before
possess you directly.
(Nail it hard)
Let them possess me directly.
Don't make your acting
too greasy.
Nor too childish.
I'll keep it a bit green.
Maintain the feeling
of a 17 or 18-year-old, okay?
That was ten years ago.
(Rehearsing The Party)
I've already noticed her.
I also feel like I can see him.
(Rehearsing The Party)
(Can't hold it in at all)
(The atmosphere lasts
less than three seconds)
(Rehearsing The Party)
(Long legs that can't stretch out)